http://www.arachnoiditis.co.uk/index.php/disclaimer-privacy-policy

Facebook
Arachnoiditis.co.uk
A quiet web of suffering and conspiracy
HomeOur AimsContact UsInformationMedical PapersEpidural Steroid InjectionsDocuments and InformationBenefit Information UKPain Management TipsLinks to Web ResourcesStoriesMike FeehanVideosPrivacy
HomeOur AimsContact UsInformationMedical PapersEpidural Steroid InjectionsDocuments and InformationBenefit Information UKPain Management TipsLinks to Web ResourcesStoriesMike FeehanVideosPrivacy
Disclaimer & Privacy Policy
Arachnoiditis.co.uk sole proprietor, Mike Feehan use reasonable efforts to include and up-date information on this website. It cannot, however, guarantee its accuracy or completeness. Arachnoiditis.co.uk and Mike Feehan, its suppliers and other parties involved in creating and delivering this website's contents, are not liable for any damages arising from the use of this site.
THIS WEB SITE IS NOT DESIGNED TO, AND DOES NOT, PROVIDE MEDICAL ADVICE. All content ("Content"), including text, graphics, images and information available on or through this Web site are for general informational purposes only. The Content is not intended to be a substitute for professional medical advice, diagnosis or treatment. NEVER DISREGARD PROFESSIONAL MEDICAL ADVICE, OR DELAY IN SEEKING IT, BECAUSE OF SOMETHING YOU HAVE READ ON THIS WEB SITE. NEVER RELY ON INFORMATION ON THIS WEB SITE IN PLACE OF SEEKING PROFESSIONAL MEDICAL ADVICE.
Arachnoiditis.co.uk and Mike Feehan IS NOT RESPONSIBLE OR LIABLE FOR ANY ADVICE, COURSE OF TREATMENT, DIAGNOSIS OR ANY OTHER INFORMATION, SERVICES OR PRODUCTS THAT YOU OBTAIN THROUGH THIS SITE.
Confirm Information With Other Sources and Your Doctor: You are encouraged to confer with your doctor with regard to information contained on or through this Web site. After reading articles or other Content from this Web site, you are encouraged to review the information carefully with your professional healthcare provider.
External Links Disclaimer
This material is produced by people and organisations not connected to Arachnoiditis.co.uk and Mike Feehan. While reasonable care was taken when selecting it, no guarantee or warranty can be given as to the accuracy or appropriateness of information.
Copyright Information
All pages, documents and graphics within Arachnoiditis.co.uk, unless otherwise stated. Data which has been gathered and included in these pages by Arachnoiditis.co.uk and Mike Feehan may be used for the purposes of personal or educational use or private research only, but not for any commercial purpose.
Mike Feehan is not Medically qualified however he is a diagnosed sufferer of Arachnoiditis and his research into the disease is recognised by the qualified expert practitioners who have offered articles and information for this his site.
Data Protection and your privacy
PRIVACY: Arachnoiditis.co.uk and Mike Feehan are committed to protecting the privacy of those using our internet site and the confidentiality of the personal information which web site visitors may provide us.
Arachnoiditis.co.uk and Mike Feehan does not sell, trade or rent personal information or share personal information with third parties unrelated to it.
If you contact us via our web site,your name, address, e-mail address and other information are kept by us and used to send you the appropriate information or to help deliver the relevant service requested.
We may also use this contact information to let you know about improvements to our sites and services. If you would rather not receive this information, please e-mail us at This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
COOKIES: We only use cookies in a limited manner to gather web site statistics. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information.
IP ADDRESS: When a visitor requests pages at any Arachnoiditis.co.uk site, our web servers automatically recognize the browser's domain name and IP address as most web sites do. This information is collected for statistical and diagnostic purposes only.
More detailed information about the Data Protection Act 1998 is available on the Data Protection Commissioner's website at www.dataprotection.gov.uk
EU Cookie Policy
Site funding and banner advertising.
The site is maintained by Mr Mike Feehan and contains no advertising for profit nor any banner advertising all articles and graphics including the site building has been offered free of charge. Donations are requested for the upkeep of the website and to help with running costs. This helps to cover telephone calls to those in need of assistance and helps towards research and obtaining medical papers, but this is strictly non commercial and not for profit.
About Arachnoiditis
What is Arachnoiditis?What can cause it?What's the symptoms?There is helpLinks to Web Resources
Our Stories
Please take a look at some of our members stories.  You might gain some encouragement from what they have to say.
Disclaimer
THIS WEB SITE IS NOT DESIGNED TO, AND DOES NOT, PROVIDE MEDICAL ADVICE. All content ("Content"), including text, graphics, images and information available on or through this Web site are for general informational purposes only. Read More
HomeOur AimsInformationStoriesVideosPrivacy
(c) 2013 Arachnoiditis.co.uk - Site by She Online
